[
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If my grandfather were younger, he ____ so many things.",
			"optionA":"wouldn't forget",
			"optionB":"didn't forget",
			"optionC":"fotgot",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If I ____ more money, I would buy a new car.",
			"optionA":"would have",
			"optionB":"had",
			"optionC":"wouldn't have",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If she had an umbrella, she ____ wet.",
			"optionA":"got",
			"optionB":"didn't get",
			"optionC":"wouldn't get",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If we ____ a car, we would get there in 30 minutes.",
			"optionA":"had",
			"optionB":"would have",
			"optionC":"wouldn't have",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I ____ more careful if I were you.",
			"optionA":"was",
			"optionB":"would be",
			"optionC":"were",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If animals could talk, I wonder what they ____.",
			"optionA":"said",
			"optionB":"say",
			"optionC":"would say",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If she ____ harder, she would make more money.",
			"optionA":"worked",
			"optionB":"will work",
			"optionC":"would work",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If he changed jobs, he ____ much happier.",
			"optionA":"will be",
			"optionB":"would be",
			"optionC":"were",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If it wasn't raining, we ____ to the beach.",
			"optionA":"went",
			"optionB":"didn't go",
			"optionC":"would go",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"You wouldn't feel so tired if you ____ more.",
			"optionA":"slept",
			"optionB":"will sleep",
			"optionC":"would sleep",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If his nose were smaller, he ____ very handsome.",
			"optionA":"were",
			"optionB":"would be",
			"optionC":"was",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I would come if I ____ a car.",
			"optionA":"would have",
			"optionB":"wouldn't have",
			"optionC":"had",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If she ____, she would tell him.",
			"optionA":"knew",
			"optionB":"knows",
			"optionC":"know",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If his parents didn't give him money, he ____ so much.",
			"optionA":"went out",
			"optionB":"wouldn't go out",
			"optionC":"didn't go out",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If she ____ me, she would have told me.",
			"optionA":"will believe",
			"optionB":"wouldn't believe",
			"optionC":"didn't believe",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"He wouldn't say that if he ____ it.",
			"optionA":"didn't mean",
			"optionB":"wouldn't mean",
			"optionC":"means",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I ____ on a trip around the world if I won the lottery.",
			"optionA":"go",
			"optionB":"would go",
			"optionC":"went",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I ____ that if I were you.",
			"optionA":"didn't do",
			"optionB":"did",
			"optionC":"would not do",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If these walls ____ thicker, we wouldn't hear the neighbors.",
			"optionA":"were",
			"optionB":"would be",
			"optionC":"was",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If I were a millionaire, ____ a mansion.",
			"optionA":"I didn't buy",
			"optionB":"I'd buy",
			"optionC":"I'm going to buy",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	}
]